{
    "id": "c21507e999404b9f80a453a436682ae0",
    "title": "Reflexive Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "His letters are all about ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "himself",
                "him",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f24c16d187d549d881e1225cb292e68f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Peter, if you work like this, you will make ……………….. ill.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "yourself",
                "yourselves"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7df33ac0eda040a987f7df87a21fbcf1"
        },
        {
            "question": "They talk to …………………. a lot.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "themself",
                "themselves"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "14733a93da8940b69273a04c1836f768"
        },
        {
            "question": "How long have you guys known ………………….?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "yourself",
                "yourselves",
                "each other"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "227047052a6a446d8af52a301b1f6264"
        },
        {
            "question": "These shoes are designed for sprinters like …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "you",
                "yourself",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5bc3f8b490a9421fb7f9748eb8716e54"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you ………………….. on Sundays?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shave",
                "shave yourself"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c67a05a9f05f4682aaf36ab21ebc4293"
        },
        {
            "question": "She took her dog with ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "herself"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7a6bdf38489b4454a4773606684ce877"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are very selfish. You only think of ……………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "you",
                "yourself"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d8511d8642554eb7bb8269d150b18042"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am quite pleased with ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "myself"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b355cc1cf6d440e493672da1c7269c4d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Everybody came early except ………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "myself",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ec58e664d9e741398ca1bf611a1a693c"
        }
    ]
}